teeoff.com 2014-07-15

# Privacy Policy | TeeOff.com

######  PRIVACY POLICY 

EFFECTIVE DATE: APRIL 8, 2013 

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected by the "EZLinks Platforms", including EZLinks.com, TeeOff.com and all other websites, applications, online services, and other interactive features or downloads that are operated by EZLinks Golf, Inc. ("EZLinks") and that post a link to this privacy policy, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or otherwise. This Privacy Policy also covers information collected by EZLinks offline. This Privacy Policy explains our information collection practices, such as the types of information we collect and how we may use that information. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review the Terms of Use, which governs your use of the EZLinks Platforms. 

######  Table of Contents 

  * Overview
  * Registration and Other Information You Provide
  * Information Third Parties Provide About You
  * Social Media/Integration With Third Party Platforms
  * Public Forums and User Content
  * Information We Collect Automatically
  * Cookies and Similar Technologies
  * How We Use Information About You
  * Information Sharing
  * Third Party Ad Networks and Analytics Providers
  * Updating Your Account
  * Third Party Content and Our Content Found Outside of the EZLinks Platform
  * Security
  * Consent to Transfer
  * Changes to This Privacy Policy
  * California Residents - Your California Privacy Rights

######  OVERVIEW 

**THIS INITIAL SUMMARY OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY HIGHLIGHTS SOME IMPORTANT POINTS REGARDING COLLECTION AND SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION AND THIRD PARTIES WHO MAY SET COOKIES AND COLLECT INFORMATION THROUGH THE EZLINKS PLATFORMS. PLEASE REVIEW OUR FULL PRIVACY POLICY BELOW BEFORE USING THE EZLINKS PLATFORMS.**

We primarily use the information we collect through the EZLinks Platforms to help you book tee times and purchase products through the EZLinks Platform and to communicate with you regarding news, special offers and other information. Click here for more details. 

We may share the information we collect through the EZLinks Platforms with our vendors and partners, including marketing partners and the golf courses at which you reserve tee times using the EZLinks Platforms. We may also share information about you for legal and business reasons. Click here for more details. If you are a California Resident, you may request additional information; please click here for more details. 

The EZLinks Platforms may contain content served by third parties, including videos and advertisements, and we work with third party service providers to serve EZLinks advertisements elsewhere online. In connection with serving content and providing analytics and advertising services, third parties may collect certain information about your visits to this or other web sites and we may receive information regarding the use of the EZLinks Platforms and the effectiveness of our advertisements. These advertising networks, advertisers, ad agencies, analytics service providers and other vendors may set and access their own tracking devices (including cookies and web beacons) and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you and your online browsing activities. Click here for additional information. Some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp") or [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ "http://www.aboutads.info/choices/") which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an "opt-out" by participating companies. 

The EZLinks Platforms may contain features that enable interaction between you, the EZLinks Platforms and third party platforms and features. Click here for further details. 

######  INFORMATION COLLECTION 

######  1\. Registration and Other Information You Provide 

The EZLinks Platforms may collect "Personal Information" (information that identifies you as a specific individual, such as your full name or e-mail address), account information (password or other information that helps us confirm that it is you accessing your account) and demographic or other information (such as your zip code and information about your interests and preferences). We will also collect payment information if you choose to purchase products or services through the EZLinks Platforms. We may also collect information, including Personal Information, about other members of your golfing party which you may submit to us when you use the EZLinks Platforms. If we combine demographic or similar information with the Personal Information we collect, we will treat it as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. 

Our services are general audience services and are not intended for individuals younger than the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from individuals younger than the age of 13. If EZLinks discovers that it has inadvertently collected personal information from anyone younger than the age of 13, it will delete that information. In addition, you must be at least 18 years of age to make a purchase through the EZLinks Platforms. 

######  2\. Information Third Parties Provide About You 

We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, someone may provide information about you in order to reserve a golf tee time on your behalf or to send you information or a gift card through the EZLinks Platforms. We may combine this information in our database and we may use it to contact you about a reserved tee time or other product purchased for you, or to offer you products or services, or for similar purposes. Third parties also may forward your information to us; for example, if you are using a service that uses the EZLinks Platforms or an EZLinks application program interface (API) to present available golf tee times. We also may supplement the information we collect with outside records from third parties. If we combine the information we receive from others with information we collect through the EZLinks Platforms, we will apply this Privacy Policy to the combined information. 

The EZLinks Platforms may permit you to interact with a third party site or service, such as enabling you to "like" us on another site or "share" content from an EZLinks Platform with other sites. If you choose to "like" or "share" content or to otherwise post information from or via the EZLinks Platforms to a third party site or service, that information may be publicly displayed, and the third party may have access to certain information about you and your use of the EZLinks Platforms. Similarly, if you interact with us through a third party site, we may have access to information about you (for example, if you "like" or "follow" our page on a third party site). 

You may also choose to use a social media tool offered by a third party, but available on an EZLinks Platform (such as posting a review or logging into the EZLinks Platforms with your username and password for another site). Use of such a feature may allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including Personal Information. When you choose to use a social media tool available on an EZLinks Platform, you may be opting to link your activities on the EZLinks Platform with a third party site or service. That third party may collect information about your visits to the EZLinks Platforms and may publish that activity to your profile or similar feature on that third party site (such as if you choose to share one of your golf course reviews from the EZLinks Platforms with your connections on the third party site). The information we collect is subject to this Privacy Policy. The information collected and stored by the third party remains subject to the third party's privacy practices, including whether the third party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third party site. 

######  4\. Public Forums and User Content 

The EZLinks Platforms may provide features through which you can publicly post content (comments, golf scores, messages, images, videos, text or other material). If you post any content through the EZLinks Platforms or otherwise submit any content to EZLinks, you grant to us a license as set forth in the Terms of Use. 

Note that anything you post publicly may be viewed by others. If you choose to voluntarily disclose Personal Information or other information publicly, that information will be considered public information and the protections of this Privacy Policy will not apply. 

######  5\. Information We Collect Automatically 

EZLinks, and our third party service providers (including analytics providers and third party content providers), may automatically collect certain "Usage Information" whenever you visit or interact with the EZLinks Platforms. "Usage Information" typically includes the browser and operating system you may be using, the URL or advertisement that referred you to the EZLinks Platforms (if applicable), the search terms you entered into a search engine that lead you to the EZLinks Platforms (if applicable), all of the areas within the EZLinks Platforms that you visit, and the time of day you used the EZLinks Platform, among other information relating to your use of the EZLinks Platforms. We may use Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including analyzing and improving the EZLinks Platforms and products, to provide special offers, and to select appropriate content to display to you. 

In addition, we automatically collect your IP address or other unique identifier ("Device Identifier") for any computer, mobile phone or tablet, or other device you may use to access the EZLinks Platforms. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned or connected to the device you use to access a Service, and our servers identify your device by its Device Identifier. Some mobile service providers may also provide us or our third party service providers with information regarding the physical location of the device used to access a Service. Usage Information is generally non-identifying, but if we associate it with you as a specific and identifiable person, we treat it as Personal Information. 

######  6\. Cookies and Similar Technologies 

The EZLinks Platforms may include the following tracking technologies, and similar technologies, and which may be set and controlled by us or by our third party providers: 

Cookies: A cookie is a data file placed on your computer or other device when you visit the EZLinks Platforms or otherwise access our online content. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, remembering you and your preferences, tracking your visits to our web pages, and facilitating your check-out and purchases. We employ Adobe Flash cookies in certain situations where we use Flash to provide some content such as video clips or animation. We do not use Flash cookies to serve interest-based advertising. For more information about Flash and the privacy choices Adobe offers, visit [http://www.macromedia.com](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). If you choose to disable cookies or to adjust your Flash privacy settings, some features of the EZLinks Platforms may not function properly. 

Web Beacons: Web beacons are small graphic images or other web programming code that may be found within the EZLinks Platforms and our communications with you. Web beacons are used to recognize certain types of information on your computer such as cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, and a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the EZLinks Platform, to monitor how users navigate the EZLinks Platform, and to count whether an e-mail we sent was opened. Web beacons may collect certain Personal Information (for example, the email address associated with an email message). 

An Embedded Script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the EZLinks Platform, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your computer or other device and is deactivated or deleted when you disconnect from the EZLinks Platforms. 

######  HOW WE USE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU 

We use information about you, including Personal Information and Usage Information, to: (1) process a transaction, including the purchase or reservation of a golf tee time or your registration with the EZLinks Platforms, including verifying information you provide is active and valid; (2) allow you to participate in features we offer or to provide related customer service (for example, to respond to your questions, complaints or comments); (3) tailor content, recommendations and offers we display to you; (4) send you information regarding EZLinks or information from us relating to a third party; (5) improve the EZLinks Platforms and our products, including asking you to participate in surveys, and for internal business purposes; (6) contact you with regard to your use of the EZLinks Platforms including, in our discretion, changes to our policies; and (7) as described in this Privacy Policy and for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent. 

######  INFORMATION SHARING 

We may share the Personal Information we collect through the EZLinks Platforms with our subsidiaries and affiliates, and our vendors and partners, including marketing partners and the golf courses at which you - or a friend on your behalf - reserve tee times using the EZLinks Platforms. California Residents: for further information regarding requesting additional information regarding third parties with whom we share Personal Information for their marketing purposes, please click here. 

In addition, we may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information and Usage Information with third parties, including advertisers, content providers, and analytics providers; and third parties may collect non-Personal Information when you visit the EZLinks Platforms. 

We also may share the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy and: 

In connection with a  _business transfer_ , such as another company that may purchase all or substantially all of the assets we use to provide the EZLinks Platforms to you (this includes disclosure during the due diligence process). 

_For legal related reasons_ , such as in response to a subpoena or when required by law, to defend our rights or to protect the personal safety, rights, property or security of any organization or individual, or in response to a written request from law enforcement regarding an investigation into criminal activity that may have occurred through or in any way using the EZLinks Platforms. We may also provide information to defend against any assertion of breach of our Terms of Use or other policies applicable to the EZLinks Platforms or to a claimed owner of intellectual property who claims that content you provided infringes on their rights. We may use Device Identifiers, including IP addresses, to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, Internet service providers, wireless service providers or law enforcement agencies in our discretion. 

In connection with a  _sweepstakes, contest or promotion_. By participating in a promotion we offer, you are agreeing to governing terms, conditions or official rules, which may contain specific requirements of you, including allowing sponsor(s) to use your name, voice, likeness or other indicia of persona in advertising or marketing. If you choose to enter a promotion, Personal Information, such as your name and shipping address, may be disclosed to third parties or the public, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the official rules, such as on a winners list. 

######  THIRD PARTY AD NETWORKS AND ANALYTICS PROVIDERS 

The EZLinks Platforms may contain content served by third parties, including videos and advertisements, and we work with vendors (including network advertisers, ad agencies, and analytics companies) to provide us with information regarding traffic on the EZLinks Platform, to serve our advertisements elsewhere online, and to provide us with information regarding the use of the EZLinks Platforms and the effectiveness of our advertisements. For example, if you clicked on one of our advertisements that led you to the EZLinks Platform, our service provider(s) may be able to tell us which advertisement you clicked on and where you were viewing the advertisement. In connection with serving content and providing analytics and advertisement services, third parties may collect certain information about your visits to the EZLinks Platforms or other web sites. These third parties may set and access their own tracking technologies (including cookies and web beacons) [Link to those sections of this policy] and may otherwise collect or have access to your Device Identifier, Usage Information and related information about you (such as your general interest in golf). Cookies and web beacons, including those set by third party network advertisers, may be used to, among other things, target advertisements, prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times and to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you. We may share Device Identifier and Usage Information about visitors with third party advertising companies, analytics providers and other vendors for similar purposes. While we may use a variety of service providers to perform advertising and analytics services, some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp") which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the "opt-out" procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit or [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ "http://www.aboutads.info/choices/"), which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an "opt-out" by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program. 

######  UPDATING YOUR ACCOUNT 

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us. You may review and update the information you have provided to us through your account on the EZLinks Platforms . We will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases. If you make changes, information may persist internally for administrative purposes and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons. You may close your account by calling our customer service number at:  **888.621.8675**. Note, however, that if you have made any public postings on or through the EZLinks Platform, those posts usually will not be removed. 

You may be able to change your preferences with regard to the communications you receive from us through your "Account" with the EZLinks Platforms or similar feature within the EZLinks Platforms. You may opt out of receiving marketing e-mails by following the opt-out instructions provided to you in those e-mails. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your account or use of the EZLinks Platforms (for example, administrative and service announcements) and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you opt-out from marketing communications. If you sign up to receive SMS or MMS messages that may be offered on the EZLinks Platforms, you may unsubscribe from any text messages received by replying "STOP." 

######  THIRD PARTY CONTENT AND OUR CONTENT FOUND OUTSIDE OF THE EZLINKS PLATFORM 

Certain content you see on the EZLinks Platforms is provided by third parties and the EZLinks Platforms may link to third party web sites, online services or other content. In addition, you may see EZLinks content on third party web sites or elsewhere online. These third parties may independently collect data. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or business practices of any third party. 

######  SECURITY 

We take commercially reasonable security measures to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. For example, when you enter certain Personal Information, such as a credit card number and CCV2 number on our checkout forms, that information is encrypted using secure socket layer (SSL) technology, to help protect the communications between you and our payment partners. However, no method of electronic transmission or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you submit and you do so at your own initiative and risk. 

######  CONSENT TO TRANSFER 

EZLinks is a United States company. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using the EZLinks Platform, or providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen. 

######  CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time and any changes will be effective upon posting. In the event that there are material changes to the way we treat your Personal Information, we will provide notice through the EZLinks Platforms. We may also notify you by email. However, we will use your Personal Information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time you submitted the information, unless you consent to the new or revised policy. 

######  CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS - YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS 

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents who provide us personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us one time per calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year. 

To obtain this information from us, please send an email message to legal@ezlinks.com or to the following mailing address: ATTN: Legal Department, 401 SOUTH LA SALLE SUITE 401 CHICAGO IL 60605. You must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the subject field of your e-mail or include it in your writing if you choose to write to us at the designated mailing address. You must include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. We will provide the requested information to you at your mailing address, or at our option, your e-mail address in response. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information. 

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, you can contact us by calling our customer service number at:  **855.383.3633**.
